



# PETER LUK

Mostly User Experience Designer Sometimes Graphics Designer

I have over 4 years of user experience design, user testing, rapid prototyping, visual design, and brand development experiences in both corporate and agile environment. My method of practice revolves around user centered design principles that are backed by research based on the users' needs as well as the business goals.

## Selected Experience

#### Software used:

Adobe XD, Unity, Adobe Photoshop, Adobe After Effects, Adobe Illustrator, Sketch, Invision, Balsamiq

## Electronic Arts (EA)

Associate UX Designer UX Designer I

January 2018 - July 2018 July 2018 - Present

- -Successfully guided UX requirements for an AAA title, NHL 19 which was welcomed with positive reviews upon release.
- -Drove designs to final products through working closely with core leads, production, and development teams.
- -Monitored and review current design system features to improve quality for user satisfaction through data collection across multiple areas.
- -Led design iterations and produce site maps, user flows, user stories, and wireframes (low to high fidelity) for the new game modes while coordinating with production and development teams to ensure feedback is being incorporated in the design.
- -Assisted with the planning and execution of UX roadmap throughout pre-production to post production.
- -Communicating with multiple teams to ensure UX principles are followed and meets the original intent of the design throughout production.
- -Led UX for Hockey Ultimate Team (HUT) onboarding
- -Led UX evaluation for multiple game modes to identify and provide solutions for areas that requires improvement for product owners and multiple disciplinary teams.

# Software used:

Axure, Adobe Illustrator, Adobe Photoshop, Adobe XD, VSTS, Microsoft Suite, Balsamiq, Sketch, Invision

### Microsoft

Lead UX Designer Intern

April 2017 - September 2017

- -Lead UX designer for an partnership application with TransLink to help create an iOS app that will be the foundation of future TransLink related projects. Met weekly with TransLink management team to discuss implementation strategy for design.
- -Developed and delivered wireframes, process flows, mock ups, user journey, prototypes and site maps to support development team.
- -Created visual assets for application and marketing team based on iOS and TransLink branding quidelines while also incorporating Microsoft's Inclusive design quideline.
- -Conducted and delivered findings of user testing to help the team identify users' challenges and feedback on authentication project by working closely with TransLink technology division to generate user data from the user testing sessions and create action items based on the data.

## Software used:

Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Illustrator, Axure, Balsamiq, JIRA, Sketch, Invision, Balsamiq

## Black Berry

Interaction Designer | Graphic Designer

May 2016 - March 2017

- -Worked daily with an agile team of developers and designers to determine, communicate, and QA test web UI and functionality as well as further investigating into old JIRAs for revision.
- -Developed and delivered wireframes, process flows, mock ups, user journey, prototypes and site maps to support development team.
- -Led usability research to observe patterns in users' interactions as well as creating the beta test survey for gathering further data on potential users.
- -Conducted and delivered findings of user testing to help the team identify users' challenges and feedback on authentication project.
- -Worked with product & research team to define research methodologies and participated in user testing or fieldwork and the presentation of findings as required.
- -Researched and developed new branding, logos, and brand guidelines. Designed and produced visual assets for new releases.





# PETER LUK

Mostly User Experience Designer Sometimes Graphics Designer

## Selected Experience

#### Software used:

Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Illustrator, Adobe After Effects, Maya

#### Languages:

HTML5/CSS3

#### Evilnut Technology

Concept Artist & Graphic Designer

November 2014 - November 2015

Designed and implemented wireframe sketches and high fidelity prototypes through frequent collaboration with developers. Created Visual assets for application and marketing material.

Worked closely with developers to create graphics for game as well as marketing manager for online promotional materials.

Sketched and created digital illustrations based on different type of art style requested by the lead art director for the mobile game.

Effectively communicated with Art Director over game flow by sketching out storyboard and going over character's motives.

#### Academic Experience

## Web Design for City Studio-Retrofitting 101

October 2015- March 2016

For a second year information design, my team and I were tasked to design and develop a responsive website that is user friendly and easy for those wishing to learn more about retrofitting and how it may benefit them. Through researching on data provided by City hall of Vancouver, we were able to generate multiple personas which our design were based upon.

As one of the UX / UI Designer in the team as well as the main graphics designer,

- -Created up to 50 low-fidelity wireframes using Axure to envision optimal user-interaction
- -Conducted user research (detailed types of research to better understand audience)
- -Was solely responsible for the entire visual design component of the project

The design process consists of up to 50 detailed low fidelitfy wireframes in the early stages to help identify the best way for the users to interact with the website.

## Skills

## User Experience

experience design, interface design, user persona, user journey, information structure, HCI , Information architecture, surveys, interviews

#### Technical Skills

html, css, jquery, google analytics, adobe suite, marketo, google adwords, microsoft office

#### Education

## Simon Fraser University

School of Interactive Arts and Technology

My discovery of my passion and the school of Interactive Arts and Technology specifically has been a winding road to say the least. Started out with science and transferred into Business, yet still weren't so sure that I wanted to pursue a career in that field. It was when I discovered SIAT that I truly found my passion. The journey to get to where I am have made me wiser, smarter, and a better designer.